Thank you for the money you give us and the way we can talk and coordinate the ideas that you place within us.
I pray that you bless this group in front of me here and take care of them, help their health be good, help them continue to be useful to our community.
Father in those moments when they're exasperated given special peace in those moments when they're thinking, what do we do?
Give them answers, but thank you that we can be together tonight, Jesus name we pray.
Father in those moments when they're thinking, what do we do?
generic information. I mean it's the same thing every time. I'm curious, like on
something this high, when it's over a certain amount, could we start getting
more detail? I'll work with them to get some more detail that's easy to
know. Yeah, I mean, because I've noticed the last time of the time before and it
wasn't quite as big as this one, but I'd like to see a little bit more granular
on this if we could, because we're 60-one thousand dollars away.
Yes, that makes sense. Oh, we're going to the next one.
Thank you. I have a question on that as well.
Feed them up, Brian. It's been as that something we could talk about in the executive
session if it has to do with strategy, as far as the cases go.
But I'm not sure there's some stuff that we don't want to say in public because it's
what it may do to the case. So, I'm not fine with that. If we have to have executive
session just because of details, I'm okay with it. I think it's still important.
And I don't know if we establish a limit, like if it's over 20,000, if it's whatever,
I'm good with whatever the groups that we're good with, but I think after a certain point,
we need to understand exactly what some of these expenses are.
Yeah, we do get every month. Right.
This is the reason we said where you have every right.
Right. Yeah, and like I said, when it's, you know, I don't know what the number is only
I want to pretend to say a number, but under a certain amount, I think it's expected
because we're going through the process, but when we start elevating in these kind of waters,
I think it's important that we get a little more, like I said, a little more detail just so we understand.
Just in case we're asked about it and we need to be able to provide more information.
Having said, I'll make a motion we approve.
Think we're going to do it separately, don't we?
You could do them together.
What's your call? Let's do them. Let's do them separately.
Yeah, wait a second.
Wait a second. So we can vote.
Aye.
Senator.
All right, 80 DL Stratton End of the Palmer claim for the earlier licensing in the amount of $550.
Motion approved.
Second.
Volume.
E-step.
High.
Submerged.
Not another day business of any wits of residence is posted on this agenda.
Ten staff reports.
11 trustee community announcements.
Well, the government.
Motion approved.
Same.
Submerged.
E-step.
Volume.